# 1721 CHOICE CENTER DR, FORT COLLINS, US, 80525 • SWADE1227@GMAIL.COM • 720-525-5948

# **SAMUEL WADE**

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Supervisor with 2+ years of experience managing store operations and leading tech services at Staples. Proficient with 4+ years of coding experience using C++, Java, and Python. Experience with Git version control, Agile methodologies (Scrum), and the Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC). Some experience using A.I./ML for data exploration. Strong team player with proven adaptability and enthusiasm for learning.

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

SUPERVISOR May 2024 - Present

# Staples

- Manage daily store operations, Opening and Closing
- ♦ Maintaining efficient workflow and customer satisfaction
- Train and supervise sales associates, optimize task delegation.

TECH ASSOCIATE Mar 2023 - May 2024

# Staples

- Setup, diagnose, and resolve tech problems according to customer's needs.
- Perform maintenance and other services on customer devices.
- ♦ Train tech associates

#### **EDUCATION**

COMPUTER SCIENCE
Colorado State University

Aug 2021 - Present

# Relevant coursework:

- ♦ Software Engineering (CS 314)
- ♦ Software Development with C++ (CS 253)
- ♦ Software Testing (CS 415)
- ♦ Computer Organization (CS 270)
- Discrete Structures and their Applications (CS 220)
- Machine Learning Foundations and Practice (CS 345)
- ♦ Topological Data Analysis (DSCI 475)
- ♦ Modern Web Applications (CS 312)

#### **SKILLS**

C++, Java, Python, Git, Machine Learning, Scikit-Learn, SDLC, Team Leadership, Problem Solving, Technical Support, Agile Methodologies.

#### **LINKS**

GitHub: github.com, Portfolio: swade1227.github.io.

## ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

## AWARDS AND ACKNOWLEDGEMENTS

- High honor roll throughout high school
- ACT score of 32
- Promoted twice to supervisor position within a year at Staples